Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=The Maid=
=الخادمة=
=Episode 26=
=الحلقة 26=
Next time,
المرة التالية،
we won't need schemes.
لن نحتاج إلى مخططات.
No more cautious steps.
لا مزيد من الخطوات الحذرة.
We'll be an ordinary couple.
سوف نكون زوجين عاديين.
What do you mean by "next time"?
ماذا تقصد ب "المرة القادمة"؟
Next time...
المرة التالية...
No!
لا!
In this world,
في هذا العالم،
what woman doesn't yearn for you?
أية امرأة لا تشتاق إليك؟
(From today onward,)
(من اليوم فصاعدا)
(you shall be my concubine.)
(ستكونين محظيتي.)
Who exactly are you?
من أنت بالضبط؟
What is your aim?
ما هو هدفك؟
One day,
يوم واحد،
I'll make your heart yearn for me.
سأجعل قلبك يتوق إلي.
(I no longer know if I'm Ye Xiyan)
(لم أعد أعرف إذا كنت يي شييان)
(or Shen Yuqing.)
(أو شين يو تشينغ.)
♪I once fell into deep love♪
♪لقد وقعت في حب عميق ذات مرة♪
(Mom's acupuncture pouch?)
(حقيبة الوخز بالإبر الخاصة بأمي؟)
This was left to me by my mother.
لقد تركت لي والدتي هذا.
She told me to give it
لقد طلبت مني أن أعطيها
to my beloved.
الى حبيبي.
♪Heal my wounds from past dreams♪
♪ شفاء جروحي من أحلام الماضي ♪
♪Fate bestowed me both joy and pain♪
♪لقد منحني القدر كل من الفرح والألم♪
Today,
اليوم،
you seem more like your true self.
يبدو أنك تشبه نفسك الحقيقية أكثر.
♪Who will unravel my dreams so deep♪
♪من سيكشف أحلامي العميقة؟♪
♪Who will save me from this lonely place♪
♪من سينقذني من هذا المكان الوحيد♪
♪Who will give me back my lonely grace♪
♪من سيعيد لي نعمتي الوحيدة♪
Pei Ji,
باي جي,
Zhao and I
تشاو وأنا
will wait for you at the villa.
سوف انتظرك في الفيلا.
♪What I await♪
♪ما أنتظره♪
♪Which heartless soul♪
♪أي روح بلا قلب♪
♪Love departs, hatred persists♪
♪الحب يرحل، والكراهية تبقى♪
♪I woke too soon to bygone bonds♪
♪استيقظت مبكرًا جدًا على الروابط القديمة♪
♪Forgetting the lost one in old dreams♪
♪نسيان المفقود في الأحلام القديمة♪
♪This life is but veiled in mist and sealed in clouds♪
♪هذه الحياة ليست سوى محجوبة بالضباب ومختومة بالغيوم♪
♪Rooted alone in a city of silence♪
♪متجذرة وحدي في مدينة الصمت♪
♪The past drifts away♪
♪الماضي يبتعد♪
♪The future fades from sight♪
♪المستقبل يتلاشى من الأفق♪
No!
لا!
♪I dare not ask the infatuated ones♪
♪لا أجرؤ على سؤال المغرمين♪
♪As the moonlight thickens♪
♪مع ازدياد كثافة ضوء القمر♪
In our next life,
في حياتنا القادمة،
let's meet earlier.
دعونا نلتقي في وقت سابق.
No, Pei Ji.
لا، باي جي.
Pei Ji.
باي جي.
Shen Yuqing
شين يو تشينغ
eliminated the traitor
القضاء على الخائن
Pei Ji
باي جي
and rendered merit by protecting His Majesty!
وأدى الفضل في حماية جلالته!
♪Illuminate lonely spirits, becoming an ordinary mortal♪
♪أضئ الأرواح الوحيدة، لتصبح إنسانًا عاديًا♪
Hence,
لذلك،
from now on, you can
من الآن فصاعدا، يمكنك
live as your true self.
عيش على طبيعتك الحقيقية.
♪Gracefully embracing affections♪
♪احتضان المشاعر برشاقة♪
Shen Yuqing...
شين يو تشينغ ...
Pei Ji.
باي جي.
Pei Ji!
باي جي!
No!
لا!
(Prince Regent's Mansion)
(قصر الأمير ريجنت)
Mother.
الأم.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Let's go, Zhao.
دعنا نذهب، تشاو.
(Lianxin Clinic)
(عيادة ليانشين)
Half a catty of raw astragalus.
نصف حفنة من القتاد الخام.
Three liang of polygala root.
ثلاثة ليانغ من جذر بوليجالا.
Three liang of achyranthes root.
ثلاثة ليانغ من جذر الأكيرانثس.
(Dendrobium)
(ديندروبيوم) ثلاثة ليانج من جذر الأكيرانث.
One liang of dendrobium.
ليانغ واحد من الديندروبيوم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
- When all under heaven
- عندما يكون الجميع تحت السماء
- recognize kindness and kindness,
- التعرف على اللطف واللطف،
- this reveals the existence of evil.
- هذا يكشف عن وجود الشر.
- When all under heaven
- عندما يكون الجميع تحت السماء
- recognize beauty as beauty,
- التعرف على الجمال باعتباره جمالاً،
- it is already marked by ugliness.
- إنه بالفعل يتسم بالقبح.
Mother,
الأم،
what does this mean?
ماذا يعني هذا؟
This teaches people
هذا يعلم الناس
not to rigidly cling
عدم التشبث بشدة
to their standards of good and evil,
وفقًا لمعاييرهم للخير والشر،
and beauty and ugliness.
والجمال والقبح.
I understand.
أفهم.
For example,
على سبيل المثال،
the world
العالم
believes my father is wicked,
يعتقد أن والدي شرير،
but in truth,
ولكن في الحقيقة،
he's virtuous.
إنه فاضل.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Come on.
تعال.
Though you survived calamity,
على الرغم من أنك نجوت من الكارثة،
you've still suffered grave injuries.
لقد كنت تعاني من إصابات خطيرة.
Your vitality drained.
لقد استنفدت حيويتك.
Proper recuperation is essential.
الاستشفاء السليم أمر ضروري.
When I was a prince,
عندما كنت أميرًا،
my mother asked me
سألتني أمي
what I desired most in life.
ما كنت أرغب فيه أكثر في الحياة.
Do you know
هل تعلم
how I answered?
كيف اجبت؟
If not an exemplary minister,
إن لم يكن وزيراً مثالياً،
then an exemplary teacher.
ثم معلمًا مثاليًا.
Without you,
بدونك،
I never dare dream of today.
لا أجرؤ على أن أحلم بهذا اليوم أبدًا.
With you, Zhao,
معك يا تشاو
and our current happiness,
وسعادتنا الحالية،
I have no regrets.
ليس لدي أي ندم.
Nor do I.
وأنا أيضا لا أفعل.
(The End)
(النهاية)
♪I once fell into deep love♪
♪لقد وقعت في حب عميق ذات مرة♪
♪Caught in a drama of love and hate♪
♪وقعت في دراما الحب والكراهية♪
♪Trapped in self-made cages♪
♪محاصرون في أقفاص من صنعهم♪
♪To whom should I direct my questions♪
♪إلى من أوجه أسئلتي♪
♪Heal my wounds from past dreams♪
♪ شفاء جروحي من أحلام الماضي ♪
♪Fate bestowed me both joy and pain♪
♪لقد منحني القدر كل من الفرح والألم♪
♪Left me a kiss of love and hate♪
♪ترك لي قبلة من الحب والكراهية♪
♪Who will unravel my dreams so deep♪
♪من سيكشف أحلامي العميقة؟♪
♪Who will save me from this lonely place♪
♪من سينقذني من هذا المكان الوحيد♪
♪Who will give me back my lonely grace♪
♪من سيعيد لي نعمتي الوحيدة♪
♪I dare not ask the infatuated ones♪
♪لا أجرؤ على سؤال المغرمين♪
♪As the moonlight thickens♪
♪مع ازدياد كثافة ضوء القمر♪
♪What I await♪
♪ما أنتظره♪
♪Which heartless soul♪
♪أي روح بلا قلب♪
♪Love departs, hatred persists♪
♪الحب يرحل، والكراهية تبقى♪
♪I woke too soon to bygone bonds♪
♪استيقظت مبكرًا جدًا على الروابط القديمة♪
♪Forgetting the lost one in old dreams♪
♪نسيان المفقود في الأحلام القديمة♪
♪No longer waiting for estranged souls♪
♪لم يعد هناك انتظار للأرواح المنفصلة♪
♪Memories flow in the deep night♪
♪تتدفق الذكريات في الليل العميق♪
♪Illuminating lonely spirits♪
♪إضاءة الأرواح الوحيدة♪
♪Become an ordinary mortal♪
♪أصبح إنسانًا عاديًا♪
♪Next spring will open heart's doors♪
♪الربيع القادم سيفتح أبواب القلب♪
♪Not seeking a specific beloved♪
♪لا أبحث عن حبيب محدد♪
♪Gracefully embracing affections♪
♪احتضان المشاعر برشاقة♪